ruminations.com 2009-12-27

# Aaron Karo presents Ruminations.com :: Privacy Policy

## _PRIVACY POLICY_  

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our website and/or register for Ruminations.com. Please read this notice carefully.  

YOUR INFORMATION  
In order to supply you with your e-mail, we need your e-mail address. We do not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. We do not sell your personal information, including your e-mail address, to any third parties for marketing purposes without your permission. We may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our e-mail to you or as required by law. 

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, also known as demographic and profile data. We may use this data to improve our website and/or tailor your experience at our website, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in Ruminations.com, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.  

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, we may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of Ruminations.com and our website. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and website. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver Ruminations.com.  

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information. All of the information described above will be stored on our secure server. 

OPT-OUT  
If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.  

THIRD PARTY ADS  
Some of the ads appearing on our website may be delivered to you by third-party providers. Information about your visit to our website, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), may be used by such providers to serve ads to you.   

COOKIES  
Like most websites on the net, we make use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server that allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. We will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our website or services. In the course of serving advertisements to our website, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.  

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
As part of the service, we may create links allowing you to access third party websites. We are in no way responsible for the content on these websites and don’t endorse these websites. Please consult those websites' individual privacy policies and terms of service in order to determine how they treat user information.  

MODIFICATION TO THIS POLICY  
We may change this policy from time to time, and we will post all changes to our website.
